neatspeed.com 2011-06-08

# NeatSpeed

## Our Commitment to Privacy

At NeatSpeed.com we respect the privacy of your information. We provide this explanation about our online information practices as a show of our commitment to protect your privacy.   
We do not sell, rent, or share or in any other way use personally-identifying information collected during your use of our Web site without your permission.   
Results of the use of our search engine services may direct you to other Web sites. You should consult the privacy policies of those Web sites to determine how your personal information may be used as a result of the use of those Web sites. 

## The Information We Collect

Most services offered by us do not require that you register and create an account or provide personally-identifying information.   
For some of our services, we may request personally-identifiable information. The information we collect is categorized as follows: 

  * Application Information--information that you provide to us through our Web site and through other means. Examples include your email address and first and last name.
  * Transaction and Experience Information--information about your transactions with us, as well as information about our communications with you. Examples include your account history, requests for information and our responses.
  * Information from Outside Sources--information from outside sources regarding your credit, background and other relationships. Examples include your employment history and public record information.

We need this information to provide services that you request and to let you know of additional goods and services about which you might be interested. We also use this information to customize your experience using our Web site. 

We may also share the information we collect about you with third parties from one or more of the following categories: 

  * Retailers.
  * Credit Card Companies.
  * Banks.
  * Government Agencies.

In addition, we automatically gather general statistical information about our Web site and visitors, such as IP addresses, browsers, pages viewed, searches conducted, sponsored links and advertisers accessed, number of visitors, goods and services purchased, etc., but in doing so we do not reference you by individual name, e-mail address, home address, or telephone number. We use this data in the aggregate to determine how much our customers use parts of our site so we can improve our site. We may provide this statistical information to third parties, but when we do so we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission.   
As part of our service, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us who you are and enable us to access your account information so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by registered or unregistered users, research visiting patterns, and help target advertisements based on user interests; assist our retail partners track visits and process orders; and track progress and participation in promotions. In some instances, our retail partners and advertisers appearing at our site may use their own cookies. Preference and options configurations in your browser determine if and how a cookie will be accepted. You can change those configurations on your computer if you desire. By changing your preferences, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is set, or you can reject all cookies. If you do so and cookies are disabled, you may be required to re-enter your information more often and certain features of our site may be unavailable. 

## The Way We Use Information

We use your personally-identifying information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our services, content and product offerings and to customize our site's content, layout, and services.   
We may use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners, new services and promotions. You can opt out of receiving this information by so indicating in your registration/preferences file. We may ask you to provide us voluntarily with additional information regarding your personal or business interests, experience or requests, which we may use to customize our service for you.   
We may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our Terms of Services. At times, we may review status or activity of multiple users to do so. We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our products and services.   
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to manage our Web site and to enhance our site based on the usage pattern data we receive. 

## Security

We employ reasonable and current security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information.   
If we issue you a log-in and password, we recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. This is to help ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place where others may have access to it.   
Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online--for example on message boards, through e-mail or in chat areas--that information can be collected and used by others.   
No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

## Children Under 13

We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Web site, and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a child has provided us with personally-identifying information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities. 

## Third Party Practices

The Privacy Policy of an advertiser or promotional service appearing at our site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read that policy before responding to the offer. 

## Changes to Our Policy

This Privacy Policy became effective on January 1st 2008. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be communicated through our Web site at least ten (10) days in advance of its effective date. Information collected before changes are made will be secured according to the previous Privacy Policy. 

## Your Consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner we describe.
